Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Non-digitized Tapes, 1956-2001
  - II:A Private Recordings
    - Teahan, Terry "Cuz" (concertina), McDonagh, Mary (fiddle). Private performance and interview as part of the Chicago Ethnic Arts Project. (Length: 00:30:00) Original tapes are at the American Folklife Center., May, 1977 (Box 15, Item aiamm442R)
    - Thompson, Sue (flute, guitar) Interview with Brooklyn-born Thompson in Seattle, WA. Thompson discusses her life, folk music, learning Irish music in California and the influence of Kevin Keegan. (Length: 01:00:00), Sep 10, 1991 (Box 25, Item aiamm820C)
    - Tunney, Paddy (vocals) Recording session. (Length:00:20:00), Apr 24, 1980 (Box 15, Item aiamm443R)
    - Tuohey, Kay. Labeled "Interview in Her House in NJ." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Feb 16, 1977 (Box 18, Item aiamm444R)
    - Ui Cearuill, Treasa (vocals) Private performance of sean nos songs including "Sagart na Cuile Baine" in Staten Island. (Length: 00:15:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm821C)
    - Unidentified. Demo tape of unaccompanied fiddler playing "Gillian's Apples." (Length: 00:30:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm826C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "As Flowers Bloom - Tony Ellis." Private performance of one soft tune by an unidentified guitarist. (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm827C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Copy of Masters." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm445R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Dave Milefsky's Tape: Miller's Reel etc." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm446R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Ed Reavy Tape 2/Side 2/Bad Sound." Private performances by accordion, fiddle and piano with bad hum. (Length: 01:00:00), 1960s (Box 25, Item aiamm822C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Eugene's Kids." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Feb 17, 1974 (Box 27, Item aiamm824C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Eugene's Tape - Dinny's Irish Champions." Cassette letter from N. Ireland featuring airs from an unidentified fiddler, Seamus McLaughlin (whistle) and all-Ireland champions Michael Keery, age 14 (whistle), Madeleine O'Dowd, age 11 (concertina) and other children from a music school. (Length: 00:45:00), 1970s (Box 25, Item aiamm825C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Golden East Recording." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm447R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Kids in Bridesbury - Eugene's Kids." Interview with little boys about King Arthur and street games and with some women about Polish Easter traditions and Polish-Irish relations in the neighborhood. (Length: 01:30:00), Feb 17, 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm823C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Louie Quinn - Kelly's Reel" Private trio performances of accordion, fiddle and piano. Handwritten note on box: "Tom, I put a paper in the tape where the tune starts. Just give it to Lou he will understand." (Length: 02:00:00), undated (Box 15, Item aiamm448R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Master Out - Takes." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm449R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Songs and Music, Tyrone." A fiddler plays for another Tyrone man with some chat followed by many songs from various singers. Probably not recorded by Moloney. (Length: 01:30:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm828C)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Time Marks Time - Perfect Copy." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm450R)
    - Unidentified. Labeled "Tunes to Learn." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm829C)
    - Unidentified. Private performance of "Jesse Winch’s Jig" and "Tom Doherty’s Polka" and a waltz on unaccompanied melodeon. (Length: 00:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm830C)
    - Various artists. Compilation tape of private performances and commercial recordings. Musicians include: Hamper McBee (songs and stories), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo), Martin O'Connor (accordion) playing tunes and a short excerpt from a big session. (Total length: 00:45:00), Aug, 1982 (Box 25, Item aiamm834C)
    - Various artists. Interviews at the New York Fleadh with Patty Conway (accordion) and John Ivers (Eileen's father) about competition (20 minutes, Apr 1978); private performance by Dawn Mulvihill (whistle) (10 minutes, Apr 1978); interview with Michael Deeley about Irish music in San Francisco, CA. (10 minutes, Aug 11, 1978); noisy session including Mick Moloney, Eugene O'Donnell and unidentified accordion (5 minutes); interview in Los Angeles with Howard and Roz Lerman (radio show hosts) about interest in Irish music in Los Angeles (15 minutes, Aug 13, 1978). (Total length: 01:00:00), Apr, 1978 and Aug 11, 1978 (Box 25, Item aiamm833C)
    - Various Artists. Labeled "Old Timey Music Rec. by Blanton Owen and Others: Tommy Jarrell, Fred Cockenham." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 18, Item aiamm452R)
    - Various Artists. Labeled "Rounder Wind Instruments Record." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm835C)
    - Various Artists. Labeled "Tape I Sent to Smithsonian." Moloney introduces excerpts of private performances by Andy McGann and Paddy Reynolds (fiddles), Jack Coen (flute) and Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mike Rafferty (flute), Mike Preston (flute) and Anne McIlvaney (piano), James Keane (accordion), Mike Flynn (flute), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Maureen Glynn (piano), Johnny Cronin (fiddle), Gene Kelly (accordion) and James Mahon (piano), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Seamus Cooley (flute), Johnny McGreevy (fiddle), Joe Shannon (uilleann pipes). (Length: 01:00:00), 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm831C)
    - Various Artists. Labeled "Tape II Sent to Smithsonian." Moloney introduces excerpts of private performances by himself, Michael Flatley (flute), L.E. McCullough (whistle), James Keane Sr. (vocals), Mary Cooley (vocals), Joe Heaney (vocals). (Length: 00:30:00), 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm832C)
    - Various Artists. Private performance by Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes) (15 minutes); Concert performance by Moloney (banjo, guitar), James Keane (accordion), Sean Keane (fiddle) (30 minutes). (Length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 26, Item aiamm1231C)
    - Various Artists. Side A: Private performance by the Kilfenora Ceili Band, Ennis Co Clare; Side B: Music from Gussie O'Connor's Pub, Doolin. Session with Micho (whistle) and Packie Russell (concertina) and Moloney (guitar). (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 4, 1974 (Box 26, Item aiamm1232C)
    - Various Artists. Side A: Private performance by Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Martin Mulvihill (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar) in the Bronx. (20 minutes); Private performances by Mick Moloney (banjo), Timmy Britton (pipes, whistle) in Philadelphia; Side B: Moloney practices banjo and experiments with some homemade guitar overdubs. (30 minutes). (Length: 01:15:00), Jul 8, 1980 (Box 26, Item aiamm1228C)
    - Vesey, John (fiddle) Interview at Vesey's home in Philadelphia, PA. The Sligo fiddler discusses his life and music. (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 8, 1977 (Box 25, Item aiamm836C)
    - Vesey, John (fiddle), Flynn, Joe (fiddle) Private performance of solos and duets including some unidentified whistle (35 minutes); pub performance by Johnny Cronin (fiddle) and unidentified guitar and singer (20 minutes); private performance by Martin Mulvihill (fiddle) with unidentified guitar (5 minutes). (Total length: 01:00:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm837C)
    - Walsh, John (banjo) Interview and private performance in Wasilla, AK. Dublin-born promoter and musician discusses his life and music intersperced with tunes (45 minutes) followed by Moloney practicing tunes on mandolin (10 minutes) (Total length: 00:50:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm838C)
    - Whelan, John (accordion), Carroll, Liz (fiddle) Poor fidelity recording of a concert performance by Carroll with unidentified guitar and percussion, later joined by Billy McComiskey (accordion) followed by ten minutes of John Whelan putting tunes on tape at several speeds. (Total length: 01:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm839C)
    - Wick, Linnane (dancer) Homemade recording of step dancing to commercial fiddle and piano music. (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm840C)
    - Wick, Regan (synthesizer) Demo arrangements of tunes. (Length: 00:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm841C)
    - Wild Geese (group) Rough mixes from Windmill Lane Studios, Dublin for the album In Full Flight. Musicians include: Manus Lunny, Gerry (banjo) O'Connor. (Length: 00:45:00), 1983 (Box 25, Item aiamm842C)
    - Wildcats (group) Old-time music demo featuring fiddle, bango, guitar, male and female vocals. (Length: 00:15:00), 1987 (Box 25, Item aiamm843C)
    - Wilkinson, Dessie (flute, vocals), Moloney, Mick (guitar, mandolin) Private performance at Moloney's home, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 00:30:00), Jul 7, 1981 (Box 25, Item aiamm844C)
    - Wilson, Dick (guitar, vocals) Unidentified flute, fiddle and guitar recording session followed by concert and private performances of songs. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm845C)
    - Zahm, Charlie (vocals, guitar) Demo. (Length: 00:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm846C)
    - Zahm, Charlie (vocals, guitar) Demo. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm847C)
  - II:B Public Recordings
    - "Bawdy Song Lecture." Compilation of bawdy Irish and english songs with typed log. (Length: 00:45:00), Nov 25, 1969 (Box 25, Item aiamm848C)
    - "Irish House." Concert/lecture hosted by Moloney at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Moloney (banjo), Chris Davala (concertina), Joe Allen (flute), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Theresa Pyott (vocals), Tom Wilsbach (mandolin, whistle, guitar). (Length:01:10:00), 1973 (Box 26, Item aiamm1220C)
    - Slattery's. Concert performances at the Dublin pub. Musicians include Seamus Ennis (uilleann pipes, songs, stories), Kevin Cunniffe (vocals), Unidentified fiddle, accordion and vocals. (Length:01:00:00), Aug 15, 1973 (Box 25, Item aiamm849C)
    - "Green Apples." Radio show broadcast on WBAI, New York, hosted by Steve Rathe. Side A: Traditional music and interviews with Brian Heron from the Irish Arts Center and Joe Burke (accordion, whistle), Johnny Cronin (fiddle), Jim Mahon (piano), Bill Black (vocals), Nan and Packie O'Reilly, Chuck O'Donnell (fiddle), Dan Milner (vocals). (60 minutes); Side B: Concert performance with Bill Ochs (pipes), Chuck O'Donnell (fiddle), Brian Heron (vocals), Dan Milner (vocals). (60 minutes) (Total length: 02:00:00), circa 1973 (Box 16, Item aiamm453R)
    - Irish Arts Center Benefit. Side A: Concert performance with IAC workshop ensemble preceded by 30 minutes of blank tape. Musicians include: John Dillon (guitar, vocals), Dan Milner (vocals), Non O'Reilly (vocals), Mark Ross (country group). (60 minutes); Side B: Concert cont'd. Musicians include: Debby McClatchey (vocals), Judy Tibo (highland pipes), Delaware Water Gap (Old-time music), McNulty Sisters (Irish-American singers), Johnny Cronin (fiddle), Joe Burke (accordion, flute). (60 minutes) (Total length: 02:00:00), circa 1973 (Box 23, Item aiamm454R)
    - Ochs, Bill (uilleann pipes, whistle) Side A: Concert performance with Chuck O'Donnell (fiddle), Bill Black (guitar, vocals), Dan Milner (vocals) (60 minutes); Side B: Compilation of commercial recordings of world music (50 minutes); concert continued with Gina Dunlap (vocals). (10 minutes) (Total length: 01:10:00), circa 1973 (Box 23, Item aiamm455R)
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival. Moloney discusses Irish music from stage and plays solo mandolin (10 minutes) followed by other non-Irish folk performers. (Total length:00:50:00), 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm850C)
    - "House Ceilidh/Music at Cussie O'Connor's Pub" Musicians include: Micho Russell (whistle), Packie Russell (concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo)in Doolin, Co. Clare. [Needs significant preservation before digitization], Jan 7, 1974 (Box 27, Item aiamm1201C)
    - "Party at Lucy Johnson's." Session in Dublin with Mick Moloney (banjo), Maddy Prior, Liam O'Flynn (uilleann pipes), Matt Molloy (flute), Tommy Peoples (fiddle), Frank Harte (vocals). (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 10, 1974 (Box 26, Item aiamm1214C)
    - Kelly, Jimmy (vocals), Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar) Concert performance at the Tara Bar, Nashville, TN. (Length: 01:00:00), Aug 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm851C)
    - Chieftains (group) Concert performance at the Irish Center, Philadelphia, PA, taped from audience with extensive introduction by Moloney. Musicians: Paddy Moloney (uilleann pipes), Sean Keane (fiddle), Martin Fay (fiddle), Sean Potts (whistle), Michael Tubridy (flute), Peadar Mercier (bodhran), Derek Bell (harp). (Length: 01:30:00), Nov 22, 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm852C)
    - "Chieftans Continued." Concert performance at the Irish Center, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Paddy Moloney (uilleann pipes), Sean Keane (fiddle), Martin Fay (fiddle), Sean Potts (whistle), Michael Tubridy (flute), Peadar Mercier (bodhran), Derek Bell (harp). (Length: 00:20:00), Nov 22, 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm853C)
    - Chieftains Concert and Session. End of concert performance at the Irish Center, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Paddy Moloney (uilleann pipes), Sean Keane (fiddle), Martin Fay (fiddle), Sean Potts (whistle), Michael Tubridy (flute), Peadar Mercier (bodhran), Derek Bell (harp).; quiet session with Moloney, Sean Keane (fiddle), Michael Tubridy (flute), Peadar Mercier (bodhran). (Total length: 00:45:00), Nov 22, 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm854C)
    - Unicorn. Mick Moloney introduces and plays records as guest host on the WXPN Philadelphia. PA radio show, the Unicorn. (Length 01:00:00), 1975 (Box 15, Item aiamm456R)
    - "Boston Concert. Tape II." Concert performance in Boston by Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, vocals) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) with guest appearance by Paddy Cronin (fiddle). (Length: 01:00:00), Jan 11, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm855C)
    - "Boston Session/Focus-New York." Noisy party session including Paddy Cronin (fiddle); house concert performance by Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) labeled (Length: 01:00:00), Jan 11, 1975 and Dec, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm856C)
    - "Bellevue Hotel Session." Small session in Lisdoonvarna, Co. Clare with Moloney including many stories and songs as well as tunes. (Length: 01:30:00), May 31, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm857C)
    - "Gussie, Micho & Lad From Prosperous." Session at Bellevue Hotel, Lisdoonvarna, Co. Clare with Mick Moloney and Frank McTigue; session at O'Connor's in Doolin, Co. Clare labeled (Length: 01:30:00), May 31, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm858C)
    - "Party at Noleen O'Hanlon's House." Side A: Small house session with Moloney and many songs; Side B) Ragged, noisy pub session. (Total length: 00:40:00), Jun 1, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm859C)
    - "Bellevue Hotel Session/O'Connor's, Doolin." Small session with Moloney, Frank McTigue, Packie Russell, unidentified accordion, fiddle, bodhran, and songs by Tim Lyons and Micho Russell. (Length: 01:00:00), Jun 5, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm860C)
    - "Bellevue Hotel." Session in Lisdoonvarna, Co. Clare with Micho Russell (whistle), Frank McTigue, Tim Lyons (vocals), Mick Moloney (banjo). (Length: 00:30:00), Jun 5, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm861C)
    - "Bellvue Hotel Session." Musicians include: Frank McTigue, Tim Lyons (vocals) [Needs significant preservation before digitization], Jun 5, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm1205C)
    - "Session at Crusheen and Wilson's." Session with Moloney and Tim Lyons (vocals) in Co. Clare. (Length: 01:00:00), Jun 12, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm862C)
    - Session in Middletown. Session with Moloney, a Northern Irish flute player, and unidentified concertina, fiddle, whistle in Middletown, NJ. (Length: 01:00:00), Jun 27, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm863C)
    - Middleton Folk Festival. Saturday night concert at a folk festival in Middletown, NJ featuring several types of music but no Irish music. (Length: 00:30:00), Jun 28, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm864C)
    - "Ithaca - The Ox. Tape 2." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul 25, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm865C)
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival. "Session in Eugene's Room." (Length: 01:00:00), Aug 22, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm866C)
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival. "Ceili workshop, Walt Fischer, Tom Paxton, Sat. Evening Concert." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Aug 23, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm867C)
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival. "Ceilidhe." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Aug 23, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm868C)
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival. "Sunday Afternoon Performers' Tent." Side A) Session with Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), unidentified flute; Side B) Larger raggedy session with terrible bleed from the main stage and overmodulated sound. (Total length: 00:45:00), Aug 24, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm869C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Irish Festival. "Tape IV." Concert performances and session in Fischer's Pool, Lansdale, PA. Musicians include: Andy McGann and Paddy Reynolds (fiddles). (Length: 01:00:00), Sep 20, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm870C)
    - "Fischer's Pool Music Festival. Tape II." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Sep 20, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm871C)
    - "Carberry’s." Large noisy pub session featuring the Carberry family from Co. Longford including a Peter Carberry solo (uilleann pipes). (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 6, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm872C)
    - "Focus-New York." Concert performance by Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Moloney (guitar, banjo, vocals) followed by a session with Patty Moriarty (accordion). (Length: 01:00:00), Dec 1, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm873C)
    - Sessions in Ireland. Side A: Noisy session with snare drum at the Club na Muintear, Parnell Sq., Dublin. Side B: Short Session in Co. Clare at Terri Wilson's with a lot of chat. Moloney sings. (Total length: 00:45:00), Dec 6, 1975 (Box 25, Item aiamm874C)
    - "Ormonde." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm875C)
    - "Washington." Musicians include: Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion). [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm876C)
    - "The Wren, the Wren the King of all Birds." Radio Eireann program about the wren tradition in Limerick presented by Pat Feeley. (Length: 00:30:00), Jan 4, 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm877C)
    - Cronin, Paddy (fiddle), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals) "Tape 3." Concert performance at the Bradford Hotel, Boston, MA. (Length:00:30:00), Feb 15, 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm878C)
    - Roach, Hal (comedian) Concert comedy performance at the Warwick Hotel (40 minutes) followed by concert performance by Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (guitar). (5 minutes) Recorded from backstage. (Total length: 00:45:00), Feb 22, 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm879C)
    - Pat Stanton Irish Program. A final memorial broadcast six days after Stanton's death featuring a selection of his favorite records introduced by Pat Jr. and a woman named Jo in Philadelphia, PA. (Length 00:30:00), Mar 7, 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm457R)
    - "WIBF Pat Stanton Memorial Program." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Mar 13, 1976 (Box 18, Item aiamm458R)
    - "Session at Jack Coen's." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], May 9, 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm880C)
    - "Woodford Night - Station Island." Musicians include: Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mike Flynn, Mike Rafferty (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Jack Coen (flute), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes). [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], May 14, 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm881C)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Concert performance featuring British and American singers: Flora MacNeill (Barra), Pete Elliot (Newcastle), Nevada Slim, Sheila McGregor (Scotland), Mike McDougal and Dougie McPhee (Cape Breton), Almeida Riddle (Ozarks), Wade and Julia Maynor (N.Carolina), Angus Grant (Highland Scotland), Jean Ritchie (Kentucky), Boys of the Lough. (Length:00:45:00), Jul 10, 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm460R)
    - "Session in Joe Shannon's Room, Wash DC." Musicians include: Joe Shannon (uilleann pipes), Johnny McGreevy (fiddle), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Michael Flatley (flute), Mike Rafferty (flute). [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul 12, 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm882C)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. "Opening Session/Ballad Singing." Musicians include: Sean Corcoran, Mairead NiDomhnaill, Micho Russell, Mary Cooley, John Lyons, Unidentified (uilleann pipes)., Jul 14, 1976 (Box 26, Item aiamm1226C)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Side A: Fragments of festival concert; free reed workshop with Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina); Side B: End of free reed workshop; DeDanaan concert with Moloney, Moynihan, Finn, McDonagh, Gavin. Poor sound. (Length: 00:45:00) Original tape is at the Smithsonian., Jul 15, 1976 (Box 25, Item aiamm883C)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Song workshop performances with Sean Corcoran, Mairead Ni Dhomhnaill, Mary Cooley, John Lyons, Paddy Tunney, Micho Russell. (Length: 00:30:00) Original tape SI-DPA-OW-77-409.20 is at the Smithsonian., Jul 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm461R)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Fiddle workshop performances by Donal O'Connor, Junior Crehan, Maeve Donnelly, Johnny McGreevy, Liz Carroll, Brendan Mulvihill. (Length: 00:45:00) Original tape SI-DPA-OW-409-19 is at the Smithsonian., Jul 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm462R)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Song workshop with Paddy Tunney and Mairead Ni Dhomhnaill; Ciaran MacMathuna MCs "Music of Munster" segment with Denis Doody (accordion), Donall O'Connor (fiddle); Junior Crehan (fiddle), Sonny Murray (concertina), Micho Russell (whistle). (Length: 00:45:00) Original tape SI DPA FAF 77.720.17 is at the Smithsonian., Jul 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm463R)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Side A: Irish Stage with Lonan Byrne (bagpipes), Sean Corcoran (vocals), Paddy Tunney (vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion); Evening Concert with Micho Russell (vocals), Paddy Tunney (vocals), Eddie Clarke (harmonica). (30 minutes); Side B: Workshop with Michael Flatley and Colleen Griffith (dancers), Johnny McGreevy (fiddle), Jack Coen (flute), Mick Moloney (banjo), Billy McComiskey (accordion),Liz Carroll (fiddle); concert with Micho Russell and Paddy Tunney (vocals), Eddie Clarke (harmonica). (30 minutes) (Total length: 01:00:00) Original tape is at the Smithsonian., Jul 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm464R)
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Side A: Accordion workshop with Dennis Doody, Charlie Piggott, Gene Kelly, Billy McComiskey, Sean McGlynn; session on stage with Mike Flynn, Jack and Fr. Charlie Coen and Seamus Cooley (flutes) and Johnny McGreevy (fiddle); ten minutes of blank tape; Song workshop with Sean Corcoran and Paddy Tunney. (50 minutes); Side B: Some songs and a short snippet of accordion workshop. (10 minutes) (Total length: 01:00:00) Original tapes SI.DPA.OW-72-409-32 (fragment, SI.DPA.OW-72-409-16 and SI.DPA.OW-72-409-15) at the Smithsonian., Jul 1976 (Box 15, Item aiamm465R)